23:28            In Front of Shibuya Stream
Kusakabe?
Hey! Kusakabe!
Found you!
Panda.
This is awfully different from what I heard.
Huh?
About Itadori.
Nah, that was Sukuna.
Itadori holds control over that body.
That's the current story, right?
Urk.
I'll tell you this now.
No matter what judgment gets doled out
to Itadori later now that Gojo is gone,
I won't be taking your side.
I'm in favor of Yuji Itadori's execution.
22:36       (Local Time)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMalaysia, Kuala Lumpur
Sorry about that.
You must be worn out, Ui Ui.
Shall we sleep in the same bed tonight?
What?! That's so improper!
Do you hate me when I'm improper?
No way!
Sorry, I got a call back.
Oh, Nee-sama...
Sorry for calling so late.
Oh, right, it's morning where you are.
Me?
In KL.
Yes, with Ui Ui's Technique.
We nearly got ourselves killed, after all.
You should sell off any stocks in Japan
and all your real estate in Tokyo.
I've already exchanged all of my yen.
Yes, do it right away.
I doubt any of the major developed nations
will be spared from these negative events.
Japan is still the world's
#3 economy, despite all else.
Well, I'll leave the arrangements up to you.
It's fine. You don't need to thank me.
Just keep me on the inside, like usual.
I look forward to working with you again.
Bread, bread, bread!
What's wrong, Nii-chan?
Not feeling well?
23:28           Shibuya Station
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hB3F, Denentoshin Line Platform
I have to go.
Yuji Itadori...
What are you?
I have to know.
What am I?
Shall I save you,
23:36            Shibuya Police Station, Udagawa Police Box Ruins
Mahito?
Did he just say Geto?!
Give him back!
Give us back Gojo-sensei!
People believed catfish were
connected to earthquakes
and told stories of such a monster
up until the mid-Edo era.
They believed that when this
"Onamazu" moved underground,
it caused earthquakes to occur.
What just happened?!
You thought you fell in, didn't you?
Though, from the outside, it looked
like you fell back all on your own.
The greatest strength of Cursed Spirit
Manipulation is its quantity of options.
I can utilize multiple cursed
spirits semi-first-grade or higher,
and even if you analyze and
overcome their techniques,
I can just send out new
cursed spirits again.
Of course, I can also simply pile on
attacks without giving you time for that.
This won't...
If his forces hadn't been divided
across Kyoto and Shinjuku during last
year's Night Parade of a Hundred Demons,
he would have won instead of Okkotsu.
Though, I suppose that had nothing
to do with you, did it?
Give him back!
I suppose I should say that
even I am impressed.
Sukuna's vessel... is tough.
I knew that.
After all, I was born from you humans.
Shall we continue...
our discussion of the world to come?
Episode 46
Metamorphosis, Part 2
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Do you know about what
they call a "Supreme Art"?
It's very much akin to
the ultimate expression
of a cursed technique,
aside from one's domain.
The Supreme Art of Cursed
Spirit Manipulation is Uzumaki.
This combines the absorbed
cursed spirits into one,
creating super-high-density cursed energy
to attack your opponent with.
What are you laughing about?
Oh, sorry.
I just realized I had started acting like him.
We were talking about Uzumaki, yes?
Uzumaki is powerful,
but it also means throwing
away the quantity
of options that serves as Cursed Spirit
Manipulation's main strength.
So it wasn't very tempting to me at first.
After all, I thought it was just a way
to recycle low-level cursed spirits.
But I was wrong.
It displays its true value
when a cursed spirit above
semi-first-grade is used in Uzumaki—
and their technique is extracted.
How foolish.
Did you think I wouldn't notice
the presence you felt?
Our signal!
The target is...
right below Nishimiya!
Tsk.
A sniper rifle, huh?
Nice.
I also agree that conventional weapons
should be proactively used
when fighting a jujutsu sorcerer.
Back when I was captain
of the youth basketball team,
I remember my mother would
often dye my hair black.
In middle school, I met my mentor,
and I chose to become a jujutsu sorcerer
before ever holding a wooden
or a bamboo sword in my hands,
let alone a real sword.
I swung my sword relentlessly.
Because I didn't want to be
a burden on my mother.
I swung my sword relentlessly.
Because I didn't want to die.
New Shadow Style...
Put it all in!
Everything I've experienced,
as well as my future to come!
Even if it means I'll never
swing a sword again!
Quick Draw!
Supreme Art:
Uzumaki.
Wait!
New Shadow Style, huh?
I'm glad.
It's nice facing someone
with a bit of knowledge.
Kusakabe-san!
There's no point if you're
out in front, Sensei!
I couldn't help it!
Itadori...
It's you, right?
Panda-senpai!
And the Kyoto students!!
Good, you're back to normal.
I'm in Gorilla mode.
That man has Satoru Gojo...
and the Prison Realm, huh?
Apparently.
I don't know what he finds so fun about
walking around with that public nuisance.
Who is he?
The shell is Suguru Geto.
I don't know what's inside.
Hey, Choso.
He's...
I have three parents.
My mother,
the cursed spirit that
impregnated my mother,
and the man who mixed his
blood into the affair...
The one who toyed with my mother...
The loathsome—
Looks like you've realized it.
So that's how it is!
Kamo Noritoshi!
Kamo?!
Noritoshi?!
Kamo Noritoshi
Me?!
What?!
What's going on?!
The stain on the Kamo clan!
The worst sorcerer in all history!
If he's right, then whatever's inside
Geto would be over 150 years old.
Outlandish barriers,
and possession of outlandish cursed tools...
As far as masterminds with a cursed
technique to take over other bodies goes...
That seems appropriate, yeah.
Kamo Noritoshi is merely one
of the many names I've had.
Call me whatever you like.
How dare you...
How dare you make me
try to kill Itadori?!
My little brother!
Stand down, third-rate.
Don't keep me waiting any longer.
Move it!
I'm his older brother!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
It's a side effect of my technique.
I can feel any changes to
my blood-related siblings,
no matter how far away they are.
My younger brothers died.
Death.
For every living being,
that is their last and greatest change.
In that moment,
I strongly sensed the death of
Yuji Itadori, right before my eyes.
Which means that Yuji
must also be my
blood-related younger brother!
If Kamo Noritoshi has
been extending his life
by transferring bodies,
then it's not an impossible idea.
Which means I...
must use my full strength
to perform my duty as the older brother!
Blood Manipulation?!
So much pressure!
It's fast!
So this is Piercing Blood?!
Tsk!
Don't push yourself too hard.
You're exhausted, aren't you?
So what?
Is that any reason not to risk my life
for the younger brother
right in front of me?
Just asking, but you two
are strangers, right?
Worse than strangers.
He nearly killed me once already.
First it was Todo.
Are you sure you aren't emitting
dangerous pheromones or something?
Still, thanks to him,
the fight has grown chaotic.
We're taking advantage of this.
Right.
I still have two cores,
so I'll lead in the front.
If we all attack him together,
it should at least create an opening.
We must do everything we can
to steal back the Prison Realm.
Drumming—
Ice Formation:
Frost Calm!
An ice cursed technique?!
And one this high-level?!
If I move, I'll shatter my body!
Tsk!
Don't kill them.
I need messengers.
Is that any reason to leave them all alive?
A reverse cursed technique!
Their sorcery is on a different scale.
I want to go home!
This ice isn't enough!
Flowing Red Scale!
Then how much is?
Whose body do you think that is?!
I was the only one not frozen as solid!
Must have to do with Sukuna!
You're our ally, right?
No!
Huh?!
I'm your older brother.
Could you please take this seriously?!
Why don't you try saying
it once, for starters?
Call me "Onii-chan."
Tool Manipulation:
Wind Scythe!
Shit!
It's depressing that they parried
it with their bare hands!
Itadori-kun!
We're the only ones who can move right now!
We need to buy time for Utahime-sensei
to finish her preparations!
Yuji Itadori
is the only messenger you need, right?!
Ice Formation: Icefall!
We're gonna die!
Long time no see,
Geto-kun.
Could I get your answer to
my question from back then?
What kind of woman is your type?
Yuki Tsukumo!
When one person's happiness conflicts
with another person's happiness,
that's when unhappiness is born,
but when two people's unhappiness conflicts,
it usually only creates
more unhappiness, you know?
Next time, "Shibuya Incident: Gate Closed."
Next Episode
Shibuya Incident: Gate Closed
I just want to crawl into a warm bed and sleep.